<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Writing on Justin&#39;s Notebook</title>
    <link>https://notebook.jnapolitano.io/series/writing/</link>
    <description>Justin&#39;s Notebook (Writing)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 15:30:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://notebook.jnapolitano.io/series/writing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Starbucks Coffee</title>
      <link>https://notebook.jnapolitano.io/posts/objects-identity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 15:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://notebook.jnapolitano.io/posts/objects-identity/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;objects-and-identity&#34; &gt;Objects and Identity
&lt;span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#objects-and-identity&#34;&gt;
        &lt;svg viewBox=&#34;0 0 28 23&#34; height=&#34;100%&#34; width=&#34;19&#34; xmlns=&#34;http://www.w3.org/2000/svg&#34;&gt;&lt;path d=&#34;M10 13a5 5 0 0 0 7.54.54l3-3a5 5 0 0 0-7.07-7.07l-1.72 1.71&#34; fill=&#34;none&#34; stroke-linecap=&#34;round&#34; stroke-miterlimit=&#34;10&#34; stroke-width=&#34;2&#34;/&gt;&lt;path d=&#34;M14 11a5 5 0 0 0-7.54-.54l-3 3a5 5 0 0 0 7.07 7.07l1.71-1.71&#34; fill=&#34;none&#34; stroke-linecap=&#34;round&#34; stroke-miterlimit=&#34;10&#34; stroke-width=&#34;2&#34;/&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am looking at myself.  I feel the weave of my woolen pants.  The gold and blue and black threads interweave to produce a cacoon for my pale legs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I feel confident.  I feel comfortable.  I may not be a large man. I am not the smartest; nor strongest.  Yet, I feel well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The small aesthetic things produce a positive impression. My red hankerchief accompanying a matching outfit.  A perfectly cut fade.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Boots.  Leather boots.  They deserve their own paragraph.  I love my boots. I feel steady when I wear them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Social anxiety affects me more than it used to.  I think about things.  I used to just do them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want a cappucino.  He thinks I&amp;rsquo;m a fag.  I like that film.  He&amp;rsquo;s too sentimental.  I don&amp;rsquo;t want to drive.  He must be socialist.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A man should carry on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I let the associations of other men determine my preferences.  The objects, well their social associations mean something to somebody.  To me, well I watched a few films.  I read a few books.  I idolized somebody.  I guess, I still do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My dad told me to just ignore the bullshit.  To focus on what is important.  General lack of meaning and purpose is painful.  Women.  Maybe women.  No, never women.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I still attempt to find truth and reason in why I do the things I do.  I read a solution to the problem once.  So it goes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Supposedly, one can create their identity.  Society etches her identity in to me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I do not believe in God.  I ask him for help to get out of bed.  I rationalize it away as a fear response.  Mother Mary laughs from the chain around my neck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I experienced death she stood by me in the room.  Watching over my body as it descended into death.  I survived.  She is no longer with me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Drink my coffee.  Starbucks brand.  I feel better.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
